https://www.shortiescandles.com/help.cgi?f=11

Rewards:LoginAccount
FRAGRANCES
Bakery
Apple HarvestApples & CinnamonButter Pecan PieCaramel Apple CiderChocolate Fudge Brownie™Cinnamon BarkCinnamon VanillaPumpkin SoufflePumpkin Walnut CheesecakeVanilla BeanVanilla HazelnutVanilla MapleWhite Chocolate Mint
Earth
Nag ChampaOakmoss & AmberPepperberry Spice™Pinyon & PatchouliSaffron GingerSandalwoodSandalwood RoseFloral
CarnationEnglish LavenderGardeniaHoneysuckle
Honeysuckle JasmineJasmineLilacPlumeriaRose PetalsStargazer LilyTrue RoseWisteriaFresh & Clean
Baby PowderBlue Moon™Cucumber MelonCuddly Cotton™Eucalyptus Leaf
Eucalyptus SpearmintHawaiian Sunrise™Iced Mint LavenderLemongrassTahoe Pine™Fruit & Berry
Apple Afternoon™Coconut Cove™Coconut Lime VerbenaGrapefruitLemon Blueberry Twist™Mango & PapayaParadise Pear™
Holiday
Autumn Splendor™Bayberry FirChristmas EveChristmas TreeDickens ChristmasFresh PeppermintMistletoe Moments™MulberryPomegranateRoasted ChestnutsSugarplum Cranberry
PRODUCTS
Shop by Type
All Natural 3 Wick Candles
All Natural Wax Melts
Jar Candles
Soy Votive Candles
Tea Light Candles
Tumblers
ON SALE
Overstock SaleWe made too much! Save 30% on these great fragrances, get them while they last.
FUNDRAISERS
WHOLESALE
CONTACT
There is not currently any items in your cart
Items:0
Checkout
Online Help
• Candle Burning Tips
Security Information
Privacy PolicyPolicy Topics1. What personally identifiable information does Shortie's Candles collect?2. How your personally identifiable information is used.3. Who else will see your personally identifiable information?4. What ability will you have to edit and delete your account information and preferences?5. What are "cookies" and how does Shortie's Candles use them?6. What choices are available to users regarding the use of cookies?7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Shortie's Candles control? 8. What can you do to better protect yourself on the Internet?
Information CollectionShortie's Candles is the sole user of the information collected on ShortiesCandles.com. Your information will never be given out or sold for profit.
In order to purchase items from this web site, all users must first sign up for a new account.
During registration, all users are required to give their contact information (such as name and email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date, and billing address). We use this information to process orders, send receipts, and confirm shipping status.
We also distribute offers via e-mail for services and promotions offered on shortiescandles.com that users have expressed interest in.
All users will have the option to clear their personal information with the exception of their e-mail address and unique password, but storing your information is encouraged so we can provide an easier and more personalized experience on our site.
Information Use
ProfileWe store information that we collect through cookies, log files, and our secure database to create a profile of our users.
A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences and purchase history.
Consequently, collected information is tied to the users' personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the use of our site for the user. We do not share your profile with any third party.
CookiesBy setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to enter their e-mail address or username, thereby saving time while on our site.
If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site.
But, their experience can not be customized and they will have to re-enter their e-mail address when required.
All of our users important information is stored on our secure server if desired.
See our Security Statement for more information.
Log FilesLike most standard Web site servers we use log files.
This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Special Offers and UpdatesWe send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please view the e-mail preferences in the Account section of our site.
Customer ServiceWe communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account.
We reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.
SharingLegal DisclaimerThough we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, or court order.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)We do not share any of our users aggregate information.
Aggregate information will only be used to improve on services, and the general use of our site.
Third Party AdvertisersNone of our users information will be given to any third party advertisers.
LinksThis Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Shortie's Candles is
not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.
We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information.
This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Who Will See Your Information
Our StaffOnly qualified personnel that have a need to access your information for business purposes will be allowed to view users information upon their request, or upon ordering from our site.
All users' information is stored on our secure server, and requires logging in with a unique user name and password to be viewed.
This allows us to closely track all information viewed very closely.
Supplementation of Information In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.
Shortie's Candles does not share any information, but in order to process users order, we must send their credit card information, and billing information to QuickBooks Merchant Services through heavily encrypted files sent by secure sockets layer (SSL) digital certificate technology.
QuickBooks Merchant Services is only used to process our customer's credit cards upon purchase and does not use this information for any other purpose.
For more information on QuickBooks Merchant Services, click here to view their Privacy Policy.
We use QuickBooks Merchant Services to verify a users address to help protect our users from credit card theft. This information will be used only for this purpose and none other.
For more information on QuickBooks Merchant Services, click here to view their privacy policy.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and PreferencesYou can edit your Shortie's Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time from the Account section on this website. New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.
All About Cookies and How We Use ThemA cookie is a piece of data stored on the users computer tied to information about the user.
We use persistent cookies to store users site preferences, and only non-harmful information to improve the use of our site.
A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the users hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by using the Internet browser tools menu.
By setting a cookie on our site, users will be enjoy a more personalized site experience and will not have to enter their e-mail address or username, thereby saving time while on our site.
If users reject the cookie, they may still use our site.
But, their experience can not be customized and they will have to re-enter their e-mail address when required.
All of our users personally identifiable information is stored on our secure server when desired, and can be deleted at any time from the Account section on this site.
See our Security Statement for more information on our security policies and procedures.
What Choices are Available to Users Regarding the Use of CookiesAt no time is a cookie necessary to browse or purchase items on our website.
We have designed our cookies only as a feature, not to track, monitor, or cause problems for any of our users.
If you still don't like the idea, you may choose to not have a cookie set on your computer when creating a new account from any portion of this site.
You may also control which options are stored from the Account section on this site.
SecurityThis Web site takes every precaution to protect our users information.
When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.
When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL.
While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just surfing.
To learn more about SSL, Click Here.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line.
All of our users information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in secure, monitored offices.
Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
Our employees must use password-protected login to our secure server when they leave their desk.
When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information.
Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices.
Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added; our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users information is protected.
Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a well protected facility].
If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to security@shortiescandles.comWhat can you do to better protect yourself on the Internet?Know the risks.The first step to being safe on the internet is knowing what you're up against.
Most trustworthy websites will have a detailed privacy policy and as much information as possible on what information has been collected, how it is used, and who will be seeing it.
If a website doesn't have a privacy policy, steer clear.
This is the best way to avoid having any problems and can prevent your information falling into the wrong hands.Educate yourself.Search the Web for as much information as you can about how to protect your privacy. Look for a privacy policy on the Web sites you visit. A good place to start is TRUSTe -- an independent, non-profit organization with a mission to build trust and confidence in the Internet. The Federal Trade Commission has a great Web site with useful information on being a Savvy Internet Traveler along with other privacy initiatives. Additional privacy resources can be found at by clicking on any of the following links:Better Business Bureau (BBB)www.bbbonline.orgCenter for Democracy and Technologywww.cdt.org/privacy/ - Data Privacywww.cdt.org/privacy/guide/ - Guide to Online PrivacyDirect Marketing Association (DMA)www.the-dma.org/Electronic Frontier Foundation - non-profit dedicated to protecting public interest in online privacy.www.eff.orgEPIC.org (Electronic Privacy Information Center) www.epic.orgNet Nanny - child safety software that filters potentially harmful Web siteswww.netnanny.com/NetCoalition.comwww.netcoalition.comNetwork Advertising Initiativewww.networkadvertising.org/Online Privacy Alliancewww.privacyalliance.org/The Privacy Rights Clearinghousewww.privacyrights.org/Contact InformationIf users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:Phone: 775-322-5847Email: info@shortiescandles.comPostal Address: 1580 Rockchuck Rd. Reno Nevada, 89506www.shortiescandles.com
GREAT CANDLES, GUARANTEED
We are committed to providing top-quality products to our customers. If you have any problems or truly feel that it does not live up to your expectations, let us know and we will make it right. It's that simple.
EARN FREE CANDLES WITH EVERY ORDER*
For the best Shortie’s experience, sign up for our free CandleBucks™ Rewards Program. As a member, you will get exclusive access to offers, discounts, and more! Learn More.
FREE OR LOW FLAT RATE SHIPPING
We know that high shipping costs can sometimes make it hard to shop online, so we will pay all of your shipping* on orders over $49, or offer $3.99 flat rate shipping on everything else! Learn More.
Fragrance Collections
Earth Candles
Fresh & Clean Candles
Fruits & Berry Candles
Bakery Candles
Floral Candles
Holiday Candles
Services
Have A Question? Call Us!toll free at866-478-7268simplyEMAIL US
Shortie's AND Social Mediacome & join the conversation!
© 2002 - 2020 Shortie's Candles LLC
|
All Rights ReservedThank you for your visit to Shortie's Candle Company™
X
